# **Kristofer Box**

39 Glen View Road, Burnley, BB11 2QW • boxkristofer@yahoo.co.uk • 07534 046651 krisbox.github.io

github.com/KrisBox • linkedin.com/in/kristofer-box/

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

As a self-motivated and time efficient student, I can prioritise workload and finish work to the highest of standards whilst controlling my own personal projects. I am also a natural leader, happy to lead any project I am given whilst managing to keep everybody motivated at the task in hand. My work experience has helped me become accustomed to working effectively with colleagues who are both technology and non-technology minded.

### **EDUCATION**

MComp Computer Science at The University of Sheffield: September 2015 – July 2019 Predicted 1st Class degree. Relevant modules:

Software Hut (89%) Introduction to Software Web and Internet Engineering (85%) Technology (81%)

Human Centred Systems Automata, Logic and Design (80%)

Automata, Logic and Computation (76%)

Algorithms and Data Structures (74%)

Notable projects:

Project lead on a 7-person web application in Ruby (99%)

Student Registration and Monitoring Ruby on Rails Web App (92%)

Dissertation project:

• Research on Conversational Interfaces and to build an Alexa 'Skill' for the Amazon Echo using REST APIs and Machine Learning.

### Burnley College: September 2013 – August 2015

Studied 3 A-Levels during this period and gained ABB in the following:

- Computing (A)
- Mathematics (B)
- ICT (B)

# **PROJECT WORK**

The following project can be found on my GitHub profile linked above.

### TV Scheduler:

- This is an Android Application currently in development as a side project, and is in an Alpha state, where the key feature is implemented and working as designed.
- The app allows users to save and order TV programmes, set their watch status, and track their ratings. Useful for those who usually forget which episode of the series they are on.

Continued...

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Some memorable achievements are:

- Being one of twelve high achievers on A-Level results day.
- Receiving an Award for Excellence, which was handed by the Mayor of Burnley.
- Being awarded the prestigious award of being Head Boy whilst in final year of High School.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Development for Profit Panda: June 2017 – Present

I work with Profit Panda, helping them in their aspirations to become the best Matched Betting service in the UK. My roles include:

- Maintaining the website and supporting the directors of Profit Panda.
- Developing new features on the website such as integrating PayPal services.
- A few key technologies used are: PHP Laravel, Laravel Spark, VueJS, Webpack and more.

# Web Developer at Sheffield Students' Union: November 2016 – Present

I work part time updating the Students' Union website. My roles include:

- Updating the homepage when the scheduler requires, including articles and events.
- Creating whole new sections for campaigns and other large Union events.
- Working alongside the full-time team of developers, marketers, and management staff.
- Actively working on the ticketing, Varsity, and merchandise websites.

### **TEACHING AND MENTORING**

# The University of Sheffield: June 2016 – Present

I work part time for the University, carrying out many roles which have now earned me the Senior Ambassador status. These roles include:

- Mentor to three first year students, helping them adapt to university life and answering any questions they may have about the course.
- Departmental ambassador working on open days, helping potential students decide whether they want to study at Sheffield.
- Supervisor in different sessions, most notably a Summer School providing guidance to students that struggle with aspects of Computer Science, such as programming, and helping them to get it right.
- Accommodation ambassador working on the weekend before Introduction
   Week. I helped ferry traffic through the accommodation village and to try and make the process for new students as smooth as possible.

### Burnley College: January 2014 – August 2015

During my two years in college, I volunteered to be an ambassador. The roles included:

- Giving tours around the college for prospective students.
- Escorting people to their interviews on annual interview days.
- Acting as a face for the College, appearing in banners and prospectus.